const questions = [
    {
              number:1,        
              question:'Assuming we wanted to eat once a day in another New York restaurant, how many years would it take to visit every restaurant in the New York area?',
              answer:'Around 75',
              options:[
           'Around 10',
           'Around 25',
           'Around 75', 
           'Around 100'
           ]
     }, 
     {
             number:2,
             question: 'What is photosynthesis?',
             answer: 'The process of producing chemical energy',
             options: [
           'The process of gas exchange in the lungs',
           'The process of digestion in herbivorous organisms',
           'The process of excretion of toxic substances from the body',
           'The process of producing chemical energy'
           ]
     }, 
     {
             number:3,
             question: 'In philosophy and psychology, a concept intended to express the view that all knowledge comes only from experience',
             answer: 'Tabula rasa',
             options: [
           'Biological determinism',
           'Innatism',
           'Tabula rasa',
           'Educationism'
           ]
     }, 
     {
             number:4,
             question:'What is the name of the line separating Poland from its eastern neighbours?',
             answer:'Curzon Line',
             options:[
                     'The Maginot Line',
                     'Curzon Line',
                     'Oder-Nysa line', 
                     'The Molotov Line'
                     ]
     }, 
     {
             number:5,
             question:'Who do you think owns the title of the most profitable music album in history?',
             answer:'Michael Jackson-"Thriller"',
             options:[
           'AC/DC-"Back in Black"',
           'Whitney Houston-"The Bodyguard"',
           'Michael Jackson-"Thriller"',
           'Adele-"21"'
           ]
     }, 
     {
            number:6,
            question:'There is no scientific evidence to support this, but in his laboratory, German scientist Dan Frost proved that diamonds can be made from:',
            answer:'peanut butter',
            options:[
            'peanut butter',
            'cheese',
            'potatoes',
            'pasta'
        ]
      }, 
  
      {
        number:7,
        question:'In the legal context, what does the term "precedent" refer to?',
        answer:'A legal decision that guides future similar cases',
        options:[
            'A legal term for a defendant in a court case',
            'A legal doctrine that states all laws are subject to change',
            'A legal decision that guides future similar cases',
            'A legal term for a plaintiff in a court case'
    ]
  }, 
  
  {
        number:8,
        question:'Which car brand was the most popular among buyers in 2022?',
        answer:'Toyota',
        options:[
        'Ford',
        'Toyota',
        'Tesla',
        'BMW'
  ]
  }, 
  
  
  {
    number:9,
    question:'Which of these animals is immortal?',
    answer:'Hydra',
    options:[
    'Polar shark',
    'The sponge Cinachyra antarctica',
    'Icelandic Cyprinus',
    'Hydra'
  ]
  }, 
  
  
  {
    number:10,
    question:'What Pneumonoultra- \n -microscopicsilicovolcanoconiosi means, \n officially the longest word in the world ?',
    answer:'lung disease',
    options:[
    'kind of fish',
    'epilepsy',
    'lung disease',
    'ancient spell'
  ]
  }, 
  
  
      ]
  